A Guide to the Davison Fund, Inc. records (II) FA080
Rockefeller Archive Center
Davison Fund, Inc. records (II)
1910-1952
Rockefeller Archive Center
Davison Fund
FA080
11.32 Cubic Feet 29 boxes: 24 document cases; 5 card-boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for researched. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Biographical/Historical note
The Davison Fund, Inc. was established by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. in 1934, having in mind the charitable undertakings which had formerly received his personal consideration. The establishment contained no instruction as to beneficiaries, nor any limitation as to field. The beneficiaries selected by the Fund were regarded as a means to an end, the effective application of resources for charitable purposes. In general, the program developed from two motivations: an interest in the social, cultural, educational, and health aspects of the citizens of New York City and its environs (including Westchester County); and "the recognition of the outstanding importance and wide significance of certain problems which cut across national and international boundaries and which invite the cooperation and support of thoughtful men everywhere."
In view of the first motivation, social work was the dominant interest of the Fund, including child welfare, medicine and health, relief of distress, and the improvement of social conditions. It also aimed to succor the indigent and to improve the standards of agencies actively at work in this field. The second motivation found its voice most notably in religion and to a lesser extent in "projects soundly conceived for the benefit of the Negro either in the field of direct social service or through those media which seek to improve relationships between the races."
Arrangement note
The records are arranged in three series:
Series 1 - Administration
Series 2 - Appropriations
Series 3 - Declinations
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Davison Fund II records, the records of the Davison Fund itself, were given to the Rockefeller Archive Center by the Rockefeller family.
Related Archival Materials note
See also the Davison Fund, Inc. (I) Collection. Many of the records in the DF I collection are also in the DF II collection. However, financial materials, including ledgers, journals, and trial balances, appear only in the DF I collection.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IV 3B 05
Scope and Contents
This collection contains correspondence, dockets, financial reports, minutes, and manuals relating to the Davison Fund, Inc.
Social problems; Social change; Poverty -- Social conditions; Race relations; Child welfare; Westchester County (N.Y.); Philanthropy -- New York (N.Y.); Philanthropy; New York (State); New York (N.Y.); African Americans; Race and society; Social service
- Administration, 1934-1952; 1
  Arrangement note
  This series is arranged alphabetically by the type of material, and thereunder chronologically.
  Scope and Contents note
  Series 1, Administration, includes minutes and dockets of the Board of Trustees, the Committee on Religious Projects, the Executive Committee, and the Special Appropriations Committee. Also included in this series are documents of record, financial reports, and the Policy Manual of 1938.
  - Dockets - Board of Trustees, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dockets - Board of Trustees, 1938-1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dockets - Committee on Religious Projects, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dockets - Committee on Religious Projects, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dockets - Committee on Religious Projects (Section A), 1937 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dockets - Committee on Religious Projects (Section B), 1937 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dockets - Committee on Religious Projects (Section A), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dockets - Committee on Religious Projects (Section B), 1938 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dockets - Committee on Religious Projects, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Dockets - Committee on Religious Projects, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Dockets - Executive Committee, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Dockets - Executive Committee, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dockets - Executive Committee, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Dockets - Executive Committee (Section A), 1937 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Dockets - Executive Committee (Section B), 1937 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Dockets - Executive Committee (Section A), 1938 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Dockets - Executive Committee (Section B), 1938 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dockets - Executive Committee, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Dockets - Executive Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Dockets - Executive Committee, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Dockets - Special Appropriations Committee, 1934-1936 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Dockets - Special Appropriations Committee, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Documents on Record - Numbers 1-11, 1934-1936 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Documents on Record - Numbers 12-24, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Documents on Record - Numbers 25-27, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Documents on Record - Numbers 38-50, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Documents on Record - Numbers 51-58, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Financial Report, 1934-1937 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Financial Report, 1938-1942 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Liquidation, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Minutes, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Minutes, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Minutes, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Minutes, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Minutes, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Minutes, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Minutes, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Minutes, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Minutes - Finance Committee, 1934-1942 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Policies, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Procedure Manual, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Procedure Manual (incomplete), 1939 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Tax-Exempt Foundation Survey, 1935-1952 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers - Numbers 1-46, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers - Numbers 47-280, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers - Numbers 281-492, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers - Numbers 493-540, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers - Numbers 541-767, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers - Numbers 768-797, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Appropriations, 1910-1942; 2
  This series is arranged alphabetically by organization.
  Series 2, Appropriations, consists of correspondence and some reports of grantees.
  - Agricultural Missions Foundation, Inc. - Payments, 1935-1941 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Agricultural Missions Foundation, Inc. - T. H. Sun, 1932-1936 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - American Association of Theological Schools - Payments, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Payments, 1935-1942 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Projects (A-B), 1936-1938 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    Andhra Christian College; Balasore Technical School; Baparthla Training School; Briton Corlies Memorial Hospital
  - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Projects (C), 1936-1938 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    Central Philippine College; Christian Hospital - Shaohing, East India; Christian Rural Life Institute of Japan; Clough Memorial Hospital - Ongole, India; Committee on Cooperation in Latin America; Cumbum Rural Community Training School
  - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Projects (G-M), 1934-1940 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    Garos of Assam - India; Iloilo Mission Hospital; Jamshedpur - Social and Industrial Settlement Work - India; Jorhat Christian School - Assam; Judson College, Burma; Kangpokpi Mission Station; Medical Training School - Sono Bata, Belgian Congo
  - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Projects (N-O), 1936-1941 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    National Christian Council of China, National Christian Council of the Philippines, Ongole Mission Station
  - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Projects (P-U), 1935-1941 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    Pyinmana Agricultural School - Burma; Ting Li-ch'eng (includes Fellowship Program); University of Nanking - College of Agriculture
  - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Projects - West China Union University, 1910-1941 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Projects - West China Union University - Group Study of Jesus Project, 1937-1940 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Payments, 1936-1942 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    Committee on Cooperation in Latin America; Evangelical Seminary at Puerto Rico; Grand Coulee Dam; Home Missions Council; Rural Institute for Religious Workers
  - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Projects, 1934-1939 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China, Inc. - American Committee for Christian Refugees - Payments, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - American Eugenics Society, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - American Eugenics Society, 1937-1942 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - American Friends of Turkey - American Red Cross, New York Chapter, 1934-1940 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - American Red Cross, Westchester County Chapter - American Youth Hostel, 1935-1939 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Associated Boards for Christian Colleges in China, 1935-1940 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Associated Boards for Christian Colleges in China, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Association for Improving the Condition of the Poor, 1935-1939 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Board for Christian Work in Santo Domingo, 1935-1941 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Boy Scout Foundation of Greater New York - Payments, 1934-1942 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Boy Scout Foundation of Greater New York - Report, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Boy Scout Foundation of Greater New York - Report, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Brooklyn Bureau of Charities - Brooklyn Federation for Jewish Charities, 1935-1941 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Brooklyn Urban League, 1935-1941 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Camp Sloane Corp. - Charity Organization Society, 1935-1941 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Children's Aid Society - Christian Medical Council for Overseas Work, 1936-1942 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Christian Missions Service Fellowship - Committee on Religious Work in the Canal Zone, 1937-1941 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Community Church Workers of the USA, 1934-1937 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Community Service Society - Conference of the World Mission of Christianity, Madras, 1938-1942 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Congregational - General, 1935-1939 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Congregational - Payments, 1935-1939 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Congregational - Projects (A-C), 1934-1939 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    American College, Madura, India; American Council, Philippines; Christian Economic Improvement Association, Madura, India
  - Congregational - Projects (F-I), 1934-1939 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    Foochow Union High School; Galangue Mission Station, Portuguese West Africa; Indian Leadership Fund
  - Congregational - Projects (K-N), 1934-1939 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    Kobe College; Lanao Province, Philippines; Matsuyama Shinonome Girls High School; McCord Zulu Hospital, Natal; National Christian Council of India
  - Congregational - Projects - National Christian Council of the Philippines, 1934-1938 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Congregational - Projects - Paoting Expanding Station Program, Hopei Province, 1933-1940 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Congregational - Projects - United Theological Seminary at Pasumalai, South India, 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Council on Medical Missions of the Chinese Medical Association, 1935-1938 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Emergency Relief for Far Eastern Students in the US, 1937-1940 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Fa-Fe, 1936-1942 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    Family Welfare Societies in Brooklyn, Queens, and Richmond; Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America
  - Federation for Support of Jewish Philanthropies - Foreign Missions Conference of North America, 1934-1941 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Foreign Policy Association - Franklin D. Roosevelt Library, Inc., 1935-1940 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - George Williams College, 1934-1936 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Girl Scout Federation of Greater New York, 1935-1942 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Greater New York Federation of Churches, 1934-1941 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - He-Ho, 1935-1941 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    Henry Street Visiting Nurses; Home Missions Fund
    Related Archival Materials note
    For Home Missions Fund, see also American Baptist Home Mission Society.
  - International (C-M), 1934-1941 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    International Council of Religious Education; International Missionary Council
  - Interseminary Commission for Trainee for Rural Ministry, 1935-1941 (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - Laboratory of Anthropology - Payments, 1934-1938 (Box 14, Folder 101)
  - Laboratory of Anthropology - Payments, 1939-1940 (Box 14, Folder 102)
  - Laboratory of Anthropology - Report, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - Laboratory of Anthropology - Study and Survey, 1935-1938 (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - Laymen's Missionary Movements - Legal Aid Society, 1923-1941 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - Ma, 1934-1941 (Box 14, Folder 106)
    Maine Sea Coast Missionary Society; Manhattan Council of Girls Scouts; Mannes Music School
  - Methodist Episcopal Church - Board of Foreign Missions - Payments, 1937-1939 (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church - Board of Foreign Missions - Projects (F-K), 1936-1939 (Box 14, Folder 108)
    Foochow Union High School; Kambini Central Training School
  - Methodist Episcopal Church - Board of Foreign Missions - Projects - Ushagram Education Colony, 1936-1940 (Box 15, Folder 109)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church, South - Board of Missions Rural Public Health and Evangelist Project, Japan, 1937-1940 (Box 15, Folder 110)
  - Me, 1934-1941 (Box 15, Folder 111)
    Metropolitan Federation of Daily Vacation Bible School; Metropolitan Museum of Art Concerts
  - Modern Missions Movement, 1935-1936 (Box 15, Folder 112)
    See also Movement for World Christianity.
  - Modern Missions Movement - Bulletins, 1936-1939 (Box 15, Folder 113)
  - Modern Missions Movement - Report, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 114)
  - Mou-Mus (Box 15, Folder 115)
    Mount Desert Island Biological Laboratory; Movement for World Christianity; Musicians Emergency Fund, Inc.
    For Movement for World Christianity, see also Modern Missions Movement.
  - National Committee for Cooperation in Character Education, 1938-1942 (Box 15, Folder 116)
  - National Committee on Maternal Health, Inc., 1936-1938 (Box 16, Folder 117)
  - National Committee on Maternal Health, Inc., 1939 (Box 16, Folder 118)
  - National Committee on Maternal Health, Inc., 1940-1941 (Box 16, Folder 119)
  - National (Con-Cou), 1935-1942 (Box 16, Folder 120)
    National Conference on Christians and Jews; National Council of Student Christian Associations
  - National Information Bureau, 1935-1942 (Box 16, Folder 121)
  - National (M-P), 1935-1941 (Box 16, Folder 122)
    National Municipal League; National Music League; National Orchestral Association; National Peace Conference; National Protestant Laymen's Commission
  - National Urban League, 1935-1942 (Box 16, Folder 123)
  - New England Town and Country Church Commission, Inc., 1936-1942 (Box 16, Folder 124)
  - New York (A-B), 1936-1941 (Box 16, Folder 125)
    New York Adult Educational Council; New York Baptist City Society
  - New York Protestant Episcopal City Mission Society - Wiltwick School for Boys, 1937-1938 (Box 17, Folder 126)
  - New York (S-T), 1934-1940 (Box 17, Folder 127)
    New York State Council of Churches; New York Times 100 Neediest Cases; New York Tuberculosis and Health Association
  - New York Urban League, Inc. - New York Urban League Society, 1934-1942 (Box 17, Folder 128)
  - Northern Baptist Convention - Board of Education and Campus Pastors, 1934-1939 (Box 17, Folder 129)
  - Oollannore Rural Reconstruction Institute, 1936-1940 (Box 17, Folder 130)
  - Pe-Ph, 1935-1941 (Box 17, Folder 131)
    People's Chorus of New York; Philharmonic - Symphony Society of New York
  - Presbyterian, 1936-1940 (Box 17, Folder 132)
    Health Nurse Fellowship; Moga Training School for Village Teachers; Presbyterian National University; Siamese Medical Scholarship
  - Professional Children's School, 1935-1941 (Box 17, Folder 133)
  - Protestant Episcopal - Missionary District of Alaska, 1936-1937 (Box 17, Folder 134)
  - Public Education Association, 1935-1942 (Box 17, Folder 135)
  - Raymond Rich Associates, 1939-1942 (Box 17, Folder 136)
  - Reformed Church in America - Board of Foreign Missions, 1938-1942 (Box 18, Folder 137)
  - Reg-Rel, 1935-1941 (Box 18, Folder 138)
    Regional Plan Association, Inc.; Religious Education Association
  - Sa-Se, 1936-1939 (Box 18, Folder 139)
    Saint Francis Xavier University, Extension Department; School of Japan Language and Culture; Service Bureau for Negro Children
  - Society of Friends, 1935-1939 (Box 18, Folder 140)
    Mito Civic Center (Shiminkwan), Mito, Japan; Young Farmers Institutes and New Life Society
  - St, 1933-1942 (Box 18, Folder 141)
    Stadium Concerts, Inc.; State Charities Aid Association; State University of Iowa - School of Religion; Student Volunteer Movement
  - Th-Tr, 1935-1941 (Box 18, Folder 142)
    Thessalonica Agricultural and Industrial Institute - Salonica, Greece; Traveler's Aid Society
  - Twentieth Century Fund, Inc., 1931-1941 (Box 18, Folder 143)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York, 1934-1942 (Box 18, Folder 144)
  - Un-Ut, 1936-1939 (Box 19, Folder 145)
    United Jewish Appeal; Utopia Children's House
  - V, 1935-1937 (Box 19, Folder 146)
    Visiting Nurse Association of Brooklyn; Vocational Service for Juniors
  - Welfare Council of New York City - Payments, 1934-1941 (Box 19, Folder 147)
  - Welfare Council of New York City - Negro Project, 1937-1942 (Box 19, Folder 148)
  - Welfare Council of New York City - Report - The Work of the Welfare Council of New York City (Box 19, Folder 149)
  - Welfare Council of New York City - Reports, 1938-1941 (Box 19, Folder 150)
  - Westchester County (C), 1936-1942 (Box 19, Folder 151)
    Westchester County Children's Association; Westchester County Council of Social Agencies
  - Westchester County (C-T), 1935-1942 (Box 19, Folder 152)
    Westchester County Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Children; Westchester Tuberculosis and Health Association
  - Woman's American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Contributions, 1935-1939 (Box 20, Folder 153)
  - Woman's American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Payments, 1936-1939 (Box 20, Folder 154)
  - Woman's American Baptist Foreign Mission Society - Projects, 1935-1939 (Box 20, Folder 155)
    Ellen Mitchell Memorial Hospital; Girls' Middle School, Balasore, Orissa, India; Girls Normal Training School for Village Teachers, South India; Memorial School for Mothercraft; Midmapore High School for Girls, Bengal; Morioka Rural Work for Women, Japan; Mothercraft Work in China
  - Woman's American Baptist Home Mission Society, 1935-1940 (Box 20, Folder 156)
    Council of Women for Home Missions; Department of Christian Friendliness
  - World ( C-S), 1936-1942 (Box 20, Folder 157)
    World Conference on Faith and Order; World Council of Churches, Joint Executive Committee; World Wide Broadcasting Foundation; World's Sunday School Association; Brazil Council of Religious Education; National Committee for Christian Religious Education, Shanghai; Religious Education in Catholicossat of Silicie, Syria
  - World's Sunday School Association - Contributions, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 158)
  - World's Sunday School Association - Contributions, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 159)
  - World's Sunday School Association - Payments, 1936-1941 (Box 20, Folder 160)
  - World's Sunday School Association - Projects, 1934-1940 (Box 21, Folder 161)
  - Yosemite National Park Church, 1936-1939 (Box 21, Folder 162)
  - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - Brooklyn/Queens, 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 163)
  - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - General, 1935-1940 (Box 21, Folder 164)
  - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - Payments, 1935-1941 (Box 21, Folder 165)
  - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - Projects (C-I), 1934-1940 (Box 21, Folder 166)
    College of Physical Education, Madras, India; Instituto Tecnico de la Federacion Sud Americana de Associaciones Cristianas de Jorenes, Montevideo
  - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - Projects - Rural Reconstruction Center - Martandam, India, 1934-1940 (Box 21, Folder 167)
  - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - International Committee - Projects - Institute for Training Native African Social Workers, 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 168)
  - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - National Board, 1935-1941 (Box 21, Folder 169)
  - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - National Board - Colored Work Department, 1935-1941 (Box 21, Folder 170)
  - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - New York City - Payments, 1935-1941 (Box 21, Folder 171)
  - Young Mens Christian Association (YMCA) - New York City - Projects, 1936-1940 (Box 22, Folder 172)
    Employed Officers Relief, Harlem Branch, Uptown Branch
  - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - Foreign Division - General and Payments, 1934-1937 (Box 22, Folder 173)
  - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - Foreign Division - Projects, 1934-1937 (Box 22, Folder 174)
    Anandagiri Conference Grounds; India Hostel Project; Peiping International Women's Service Building, Shanghai; International Conference in South America; Rural Development; Tokyo, Japan; Training Leaders in India
  - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - National Board, 1935-1941 (Box 22, Folder 175)
  - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) - New York City, 1934-1942 (Box 22, Folder 176)
- Declinations, 1923-1942; 3
  Series 3, Declinations, consists of correspondence and some reports of applicants not receiving grants.
  - Allahabad Agricultural Institute, 1934-1938 (Box 23, Folder 177)
  - American Baptist Publication Society, 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 178)
  - American (B) - Auburn, 1935-1940 (Box 23, Folder 179)
    American Bible Society American Friends Board of Missions American Committee for the Settlement of Jews in Birobidjan American Heart Association, Inc. American Lyric Theatre Corporation American Sunday School Union Associated Negro Press Auburn Theological Seminar
  - B, 1936-1941 (Box 23, Folder 180)
    Biosophical Institute; Boys' Athletic League, Inc.; Boys' Brotherhood Republic of New York, Inc.; Brown Vocational and Placement Center; Bulletin of Research and Review; Bureau of Marriage Counsel and Education, Inc.
  - C, 1935-1940 (Box 23, Folder 181)
    Christian Farmer, Church of Christ in China, Christian Colleges in India, Committee on Neighborhood Health Development
  - E-F, 1935-1941 (Box 23, Folder 182)
    East Harlem Nursing and Health Service; Edgecomb Sanitarium; Evangelical Union, Puerto Rico; Farmers' Federation; Fifield, Dr. James W., Jr.; First Congregational Church of Los Angeles; First National Christian Convention; Ford, George G.; Friendly Relations Committee
  - G, 1933-1939 (Box 23, Folder 183)
    George Junior Republic, Gould Farm, Greater New York Safety Council, Greenwich House Music School, Greenwich House Work Shops
  - H, 1935-1941 (Box 23, Folder 184)
    Harlem Big Brother Association, Hartford Seminary Education, Home for Incurables, Hope Day Nursery, Hospital Council of Greater New York
  - Institute - Inter-Denominational, 1935-1942 (Box 23, Folder 185)